Kishore Kumar S

Associate Software Engineer

Full Stack .NET Developer with a preference to work in Java related technologies. Enthusiastic and well-organized individual with good communication skills, team spirit, and B.E. in Computer Science desires the position of Software Developer at SAP. Bringing 1.5+ years of expertise in writing full-stack code to building and maintaining cloud environments in Azure and AWS.

kishore2496@gmail.com +91-8892108809 Vidyaranyapura Bangalore – 560 097 Karnataka

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ivanti Software India Private Limited

Associate Software Engineer

Aug 2019 - Present

Development

- SME and responsible for API design and implementation of RESTful Services for the enterprise product Ivanti Service Manager (ISM) in the business
- SME for localization/internationalization for the enterprise product ISM that supports more than 20 languages out of the box
- Implemented Elastic Logstash Kibana (ELK) for internal cloud environments for developer monitoring and troubleshooting
- Part of customer facing team (Platinum Engineering) that actively reduced the open bug count from 850 to 160 bugs, leading to an overall 78% reduction in bug count over a period of 6 months
- Fixed 65+ bugs, the highest in the team, contributing to 9.4% of the overall bug reduction

DevOps

- · Assisted in migration of cloud infra from Azure to AWS Cloud
- Recreated and modified build and release pipelines on Azure DevOps for AWS related infra
- SME for Azure DevOps for the internal cloud dev environments
- Assisted in cloud cost cutting for prod like environment which ended up saving nearly \$8000 annually for the company

Engineering Intern

Jan 2019 - June 2019

- Worked on several functional tests/API testing for "Ivanti Integration Service" for the enterprise product Ivanti Service Manager (ISM)
- Built scripts and worked on product enhancements that improved and simplified the process of localization/internationalization enabling customers to use more languages seamlessly
- Actively fixed issues in wide range of areas including REST API, External Auth related issues, ISM Self Service Mobile (SSM) to name a few.

SKILLS

- Hard Skills: Java (J2EE Spring), C#, .NET, REST API, Azure, AWS Cloud, Azure DevOps, Powershell, Elastic Logstash Kibana (ELK), SQL Server, Hibernate
- Soft Skills: Customer service, Communication skills, Team player, Leadership/management skills, Critical thinking

EDUCATION

University Visvesvaraya College of Engineering (UVCE)

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Science (June 2015 – July 2019)

- Graduated with distinction score of 86% and stood 4th in the Computer Science Department
- Conducted various quizzes, competitions in college fests and cultural programs

CMR National PU College

12th Grade, PUC (Apr 2013 - Mar 2015)

HOBBIES

Gym, Travelling, Reading, Guitar, Gaming, Teaching